<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Front Page Posts</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>A world where everyone holds the power to employ science and creativity for good.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 12:25:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Vound Software partners with SMASHfestUK</title>
		<link>./../../../vound-software-partners-with-smashfestuk/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 12:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Front Page Posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[partnerships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sponsorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vound]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For 2016, and beyond, international eDiscovery company Vound Software will be sponsoring SMASHfestUK to support their mission of inspiring and developing the next generation of creative problem solvers worldwide. Vound blogged about Solar Storm, the 2016 story: “Imagine this, no more TV, no heat, no phones, no social media, the<a class="moretag" href="./../../../vound-software-partners-with-smashfestuk/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For 2016, and beyond, international eDiscovery company Vound Software will be sponsoring SMASHfestUK to support their mission of inspiring and developing the next generation of creative problem solvers worldwide.</p>
<p>Vound blogged about Solar Storm, the 2016 story:</p>
<p>“Imagine this, no more TV, no heat, no phones, no social media, the transport system has ground to a halt…How will we create power? How can we harness other sources of energy to help build a new future? Come along to South London and help us use science and creativity to solve this catastrophic problem.</p>
<p>As creative problem solving is a skill that will be in high demand for those who wish to enter into careers that involve email investigation and eDiscovery. Vound-Software.com and SMASHfestUK are working together to encourage individuals to use the creative problem solving element all of us have to come up with solutions that will help society as a whole survive a catastrophic event such as this.</p>
<p>A free STEM/Arts/Design festival, SMASHfestUK is created around a compelling story; a massive solar storm is forecast which wipes out our electrical and electronic infrastructure, throwing us back to the mechanical age: How will we cope without our phones, tablets and social media? How will we survive as our networks, power, transport, medical and supply chains collapse?&#8221;</p>
<p>The deal helps develop SMASHfestUK&#8217;s existing partnerships with software and coding organisations.</p>
<p>In 2016 SMASHfestUK have also partnered for the first time with Code Club https://www.codeclub.org.uk,/ a UK wide network of volunteer-led after school coding clubs for children aged 9-11, to give participants a chance to try out computer coding, as part of the festival.</p>
<p>Middlesex University, SMASHfestUK’s lead academic partner, is a leader in Visual Analytics and Computer Forensics, and continues to give huge support to development and delivery of the festival.</p>
<p>http://www.mdx.ac.uk/courses/computer-science-engineering-and-maths/Computer-and-communications-engineering</p>
<p>http://www.mdx.ac.uk/courses/postgraduate/visual-analytics</p>
<p>Founded in 2008, Vound is a leading global vendor of technology used for forensic search, eDiscovery and information governance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is SMASHfestUK?</title>
		<link>./../../../what-is-smashfestuk/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 12:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Front Page Posts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=613</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#160; SMASHfestUK is a science, technology, engineering, maths and medicine through the arts and design festival for young people, in Deptford, South East London during the February half term holidays. A mix of entertainment, sic-fi and immersive adventure the festival is themed around a gripping story of a unifying threat<a class="moretag" href="./../../../what-is-smashfestuk/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01.png" rel="attachment wp-att-1138"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-1138" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01-1024x682.png" alt="SMASHfestUK Web Front page Picture 2016 Solar Storm Jan 2016 update-01" width="680" height="453" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01-1024x682.png 1024w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01-300x200.png 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01-768x512.png 768w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01-600x400.png 600w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01-460x307.png 460w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01-688x458.png 688w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/SMASHfestUK-Web-Front-page-Picture-2016-Solar-Storm-Jan-2016-update-01.png 1250w" sizes="(max-width: 680px) 100vw, 680px" /></a>SMASHfestUK is a science, technology, engineering, maths and medicine through the arts and design festival for young people, in Deptford, South East London during the February half term holidays.</p>
<p>A mix of entertainment, sic-fi and immersive adventure the festival is themed around a gripping story of a unifying threat to humanity!</p>
<p>The pilot in 2015 had an asteroid on a collision course with Planet Earth and an ensuing zombie invasion. Visitors will had the chance to plan for Armageddon, whether it was preparing for survival, singing for their lives at the End of the World Cabaret, creating a time capsule or taking a trip to the Intergalactic Travel Agency.</p>
<p>2016 has us facing a Super Solar Storm, which will destroy all of our electrical and electronic infrastructure and will plunge us back into the mechanical age, while human mutations run rampant due to the effects of huge UV radiation.</p>
<p>SMASHfestUK is the first event of its kind, designed to widen participation and build diversity in science, technology, engineering and maths (STEM) by engaging young people and hard to reach audiences.</p>
<p>SMASHfestUK is the creation of science TV production company The Refinery, with Middlesex University as the lead partner. It is supported, in 2016, by The Wellcome Trust, The Arts Council, The Royal Society of Chemistry, the Science and Technology Facilities Council, Lewisham Borough Council and the University of Greenwich.</p>
<p>In 2015, the pilot year, it was partnered with the Stephen Lawrence Charitable Trust, the Wellcome Trust, Middlesex University, and the Royal Observatory Greenwich.</p>
<p>SMASHfestUK Press Release 2015</p>
<p>SMASHfestUK Press Release 2016</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Story has started</title>
		<link>./../../../theres-something-out-there/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 11:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Front Page Posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deptford]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smashfestUK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South east London]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zombie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The story has started, and as promised aspects of SMASHfestUK will be &#8216;on-the-street&#8217; participatory experiences. This is a picture from the SMASHfestUK photoshoot, which took place in New Cross, yesterday. People were a bit puzzled / startled by the zombie chasing a man in broad daylight through South East London.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The story has started, and as promised aspects of SMASHfestUK will be &#8216;on-the-street&#8217; participatory experiences.</p>
<div id="attachment_539" style="width: 910px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/ZombieRun_SMASHfestUK_WL_S.jpg"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-539" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-539" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/ZombieRun_SMASHfestUK_WL_S.jpg" alt="Zombie Run - Promo Pic" width="900" height="571" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/ZombieRun_SMASHfestUK_WL_S.jpg 900w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/ZombieRun_SMASHfestUK_WL_S-300x190.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-539" class="wp-caption-text">There&#8217;s something out there, beware&#8230;</p></div>
<p>This is a picture from the SMASHfestUK photoshoot, which took place in New Cross, yesterday. People were a bit puzzled / startled by the zombie chasing a man in broad daylight through South East London.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blog: Behind The Scenes at SMASHfestUK</title>
		<link>./../../../behind-the-scenes-at-smashfestuk/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 11:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Front Page Posts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=675</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your Future?</title>
		<link>./../../../your-future/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 12:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Front Page Posts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=805</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There’s a world of stuff to find out and try out. We’ve been working with amazing organisations, and they (and the wider Web) have all sorts of help and ideas available if you are thinking about getting involved in Science, Technology, Engineering, Maths or Medicine (STEM) subjects. Get Involved!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There’s a world of stuff to find out and try out. We’ve been working with amazing organisations, and they (and the wider Web) have all sorts of help and ideas available if you are thinking about getting involved in Science, Technology, Engineering, Maths or Medicine (<strong>STEM</strong>) subjects.</p>
<p><strong>Get Involved!</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
