<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lindsay</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>A world where everyone holds the power to employ science and creativity for good.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 14:09:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Astro-Commanders Wanted!</title>
		<link>./../../../space-scientists-wanted/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 16:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2480</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ever wondered what it feels to lead a group of space travellers through an adventure? Ever thought about defending the human kind from an impending cosmo-threat? This might be your chance! We are over the moon to have been awarded funding from the UKRI and UKSFN to launch a new<a class="moretag" href="./../../../space-scientists-wanted/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/07/SMASH_Astro2.png"><img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-2503 aligncenter" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/07/SMASH_Astro2.png" alt="" width="792" height="258" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/07/SMASH_Astro2.png 792w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/07/SMASH_Astro2-300x98.png 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/07/SMASH_Astro2-768x250.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 792px) 100vw, 792px" /></a><br />
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Ever wondered what it feels to lead a group of space travellers through an adventure? Ever thought about defending the human kind from an impending cosmo-threat? This might be your chance! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are over the moon to have been awarded funding from the UKRI and </span><a href="http://www.scienfestivals.uk/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">UKSFN</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to launch a new immersive sci/art project with young people aged 11-14 in South East London. How, you ask? The SMASHfestUK way of course! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will take over two venues here in the South East London (galactic) System during October half-term to bring an immersive and out-of-this world experience to the young people from the local planets … but we need your help! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This adventure can’t take place without talented astro-commanders to help the younger travellers during their journey. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Who are these astro-commanders, you ask? Astronomers, Cosmologists, Physicists, Space Engineers, Astrobiologists and anyone working within the space field! </span></p>
<p><strong>What would astro-commanders do? </strong><b><br />
</b></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Collaborate with a group of local young people and artists to create a challenging activity based on their work and/or research in the period prior to the event. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Help lead a group of young people through the challenges of space travel during the two immersive events. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Commit to 5 days in total (<strong>expenses paid by prior agreement</strong>) between September (2 half days, 23rd and 26th of September) and October (1 half-day TBD for training, 2 full days &#8211; 25th and 28th of October). Exact days to be defined soon. <strong>Time commitment can be discussed, so please don&#8217;t hesitate to contact me if you are interested. </strong></span></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>What will the astro-commanders get from the project? </strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Each commander will participate in a bespoke training session from the SMASHfestUK team covering public engagement, communication skills, community engagement and storytelling for scientists. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A platform to discuss their work and/or research with young people from South East London within an informal setting. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The opportunity to develop an engagement activity based on their work and/or research with close support from the award-winning SMASHfestUK team! </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Who would be the perfect astro-commander?  </strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Based in or can easily travel to London/Greater London (expenses paid by prior agreement). </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Interested in the Arts, STEM and Cultural Engagement. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Willing to engage the young people involved with the storyline created (might include: making top-notch space noises, wearing an astro-fascinator, using space-related puns and more… Training will be provided if this is outside your comfort zone!).</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Able to commit to 5 days between September and the end of October (3 half days in September/Early October, 2 full days in October w/c 22nd) &#8211; all expenses paid by prior agreement. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Happy to work with others as part of a team.<br />
</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Want to know more or want to join the mission?<br />
Contact the Mission Producer, Paolo, on paolo@smashfestuk.com with subject “Astro-commander”.</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Young Explainer Experience: An Opportunity For Young People</title>
		<link>./../../../my-young-explainer-experience-an-opportunity-for-young-people/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 11:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2439</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Young Explainers are 16-18 year olds with an interest in Science and Engineering who also enjoy art and design. Responsibilities of a young explainer are to create exhibits and hands on activities for the festival, explain the science and technology behind the event and interview visitors to collect feedback. My name is Roisin<a class="moretag" href="./../../../my-young-explainer-experience-an-opportunity-for-young-people/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Picture1.png"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-2441 alignleft" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Picture1-300x200.png" alt="" width="300" height="200" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Picture1-300x200.png 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Picture1.png 456w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a>Young Explainers are 16-18 year olds with an interest in Science and Engineering who also enjoy art and design. Responsibilities of a young explainer are to create exhibits and hands on activities for the festival, explain the science and technology behind the event and interview visitors to collect feedback.</p>
<p>My name is Roisin and I am a young explainer at this year&#8217;s SMASHfestUK: FLOOD! 2018. I heard about this opportunity through my school and, since then, I meet up once a week with other young explainers from my school. For this festival, we are focusing on three topics: <strong>Living in Space</strong>, <strong>Combustion</strong> and <strong>Water Rockets</strong>. As a team, we discuss ideas and aspects of the topic we want to explain and create an interactive presentation for the event.</p>
<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/02/34584492490_d1df619c66_z.jpg"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-2442 alignright" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/02/34584492490_d1df619c66_z-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="225" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/02/34584492490_d1df619c66_z-300x225.jpg 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2018/02/34584492490_d1df619c66_z.jpg 640w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a><br />
As a young explainer I have been given new opportunities to lear and develop new skills. Working to create an exhibition from scratch for the festival is something I haven&#8217;t done before, and is a big responsibility. You have to work as a team with the other young explainers to assign roles best fit to their skills and take into consideration everyone&#8217;s ideas to create a successful event. Time management is key. I have had to research, develop ideas and made sure the showcase is clear and relevant to the target audience, young children and parents.</p>
<p>To sign up and help volunteer at SMASHfestUK FLOOD! 2018 event you can <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdb5PjpnJzmy3ENB83L1EQrdzV_SOtXDsmaDeLuOc92Va4q3Q/viewform">click here</a> or visit the <a href="./../../../get-involved/index.html">Get Involved </a>page on our website!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Transport for London Apprentices!</title>
		<link>./../../../transport-for-london-apprentices/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1833</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We’re very excited to announce that this year we have got over 30 Transport for London apprentices joining us at SMASHfestUK! These budding apprentices will help us to showcase engineering as a part of our festival. We will have them with us all week during half term and there won’t<a class="moretag" href="./../../../transport-for-london-apprentices/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We’re very excited to announce that this year we have got over 30 Transport for London apprentices joining us at SMASHfestUK!</p>
<p>
These budding apprentices will help us to showcase engineering as a part of our festival. We will have them with us all week during half term and there won’t be a dull moment! They will be running workshops at The Albany Theatre, which they have designed themselves, to entertain festival goers.</p>
<p>
SMASHfestUK is really excited about working with TfL for this year’s festival!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Did Start The Fire!</title>
		<link>./../../../we-did-start-the-fire-2/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 12:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1825</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK is largely aimed at families and young people &#8211; but that doesn&#8217;t mean we can&#8217;t spice things up in the evening! Join us at The Albany Theatre on the 16th February at 7pm for our fundraiser show &#8216;We Did Start The Fire&#8217; &#8211; Grown ups only! We&#8217;ve put together<a class="moretag" href="./../../../we-did-start-the-fire-2/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SMASHfestUK is largely aimed at families and young people &#8211; but that doesn&#8217;t mean we can&#8217;t spice things up in the evening! Join us at The Albany Theatre on the 16th February at 7pm for our fundraiser show &#8216;We Did Start The Fire&#8217; &#8211; Grown ups only!</p>
<p><center><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/16300371_1431956586855312_417361594773873904_o.jpg"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-1826" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/16300371_1431956586855312_417361594773873904_o-300x199.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="199" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/16300371_1431956586855312_417361594773873904_o-300x199.jpg 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/16300371_1431956586855312_417361594773873904_o-768x510.jpg 768w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/16300371_1431956586855312_417361594773873904_o-1024x680.jpg 1024w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/16300371_1431956586855312_417361594773873904_o.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a></center></p>
<p>
We&#8217;ve put together a line-up of fantastic performers for a SMASHfestUK first &#8211; an adult-only show, which is, in fact two shows for the price of<span class="text_exposed_show"> one! Great value, and great entertainment for 2017&#8217;s SMASHfestUK Fundraiser. We&#8217;re heading off on tour to communities across the UK this year, and funds raised at this show will help us take SMASHfestUK to more people and ensure that it comes back for 2018.<br />
</span></p>
<p>
We&#8217;ve devised two shows to keep you on your toes, firstly Shrinking Space will be taking you on an immersive and interactive theatre experience with &#8220;Operation Doomsday &#8211; Chapter Supervolcano&#8221; What happens when the Supervolcano erupts? Can you save the world&#8230; or whats left of it?</p>
<p>
Then our second performance will be a variety show presented by Helen Arney; featuring music, rapping, explosions and even the occasional hula hoop! We will even be squeezing a bar break in! What more could you need?</p>
<p>
Although we try to keep SMASHfestUK free during the day, we are suggesting a donation of £10 or whatever you feel like paying! This will help us take SMASHfestUK on the road, and keep it going next year!</p>
<p>
Sound like something you should be coming along to? Visit our Facebook event for more info, and you can book tickets on The Albany website at the links below!</p>
<p>
Facebook event page: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/412387695769201/">Click here</a></p>
<p>
To book tickets and register your interest: <a href="http://www.thealbany.org.uk/event_detail/2032/Theatre/SMASHfest:-We-Did-Start-the-Fire!">Click here</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SMASHfestUK 2017 is Open for Business!</title>
		<link>./../../../smashfestuk-2017-is-open-for-business/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 17:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1780</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Award Winning SMASHfestUK is officially back! On Wednesday 18th January 2017 we opened the doors to The Albany in Deptford to many teachers, students and even the Lewisham Young Mayor and Deputy Mayor to give them a taste of what to expect from our 2017 festival. We had a<a class="moretag" href="./../../../smashfestuk-2017-is-open-for-business/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Award Winning SMASHfestUK is officially back!</p>
<p><span id="more-1780"></span>On Wednesday 18th January 2017 we opened the doors to The Albany in Deptford to many teachers, students and even the Lewisham Young Mayor and Deputy Mayor to give them a taste of what to expect from our 2017 festival. We had a fantastic time showcasing what SMASHfestUK is all about, our outreach programme with the local primary schools, and even got everyone involved with some slimy, explosive and murky demonstrations. We topped off the evening with an audience volunteer officially opening SMASHfestUK 2017 with our giant elephants toothpaste experiment!</p>
<div id="attachment_1808" style="width: 690px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/IMG_0193-3.jpg"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-1808" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-1808 size-large" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/IMG_0193-3-1024x768.jpg" width="680" height="510" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/IMG_0193-3-1024x768.jpg 1024w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/IMG_0193-3-300x225.jpg 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2017/01/IMG_0193-3-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 680px) 100vw, 680px" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-1808" class="wp-caption-text">SMASHfestUK 2017 is OPEN! Our evening ended with our big version of the Elephant&#8217;s Toothpaste experiment, officially launching SMASHfestUK 2017!</p></div>
<p><span style="word-spacing: normal;">We would like to thank everybody who came along to our launch event and we hope to see you all in February half-term for our main festival at The Deptford Lounge, and Albany Theatre! </span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guess what? We Won!</title>
		<link>./../../../guess-what-we-won/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 14:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What a night. What an amazing night! We never thought it possible there are so many brilliant projects. But it happened. We won! Thank you so much NCCPE And thank you so much to everyone that made this possible. The people of Deptford and Lewisham. The Schools. All the young<a class="moretag" href="./../../../guess-what-we-won/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-2.jpg"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-1674" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-2-1024x1024.jpg" alt="fullsizerender-2" width="680" height="680" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-2-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-2-150x150.jpg 150w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-2-300x300.jpg 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-2-768x768.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 680px) 100vw, 680px" /></a><br />
What a night. What an amazing night! We never thought it possible there are so many brilliant projects. But it happened. We won!</p>
<p>Thank you so much NCCPE And thank you so much to everyone that made this possible.</p>
<p>The people of Deptford and Lewisham. The Schools. All the young people&#8217;s hard work. Our partners such as Middlesex University and University of Greenwich Our sponsors such as The Wellcome Trust, RAE, Arts Council, STFC and Vound. And of course all of our contributors, participants and volunteers! Thank you again! You&#8217;re all just the best!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We&#8217;re on the way to the Awards Ceremony!</title>
		<link>./../../../were-on-the-way-to-the-awards-ceremony/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 11:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1645</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#160; We&#8217;re on our way to Bristol, feeling very excited! SMASHfestUK has been shortlisted for a national university public engagement award, and we&#8217;re off to the NCCPE Engage Conference where there&#8217;ll be an exhibition of all the finalists, and interviews to decide the ultimate winner. We&#8217;re honoured to be there,<a class="moretag" href="./../../../were-on-the-way-to-the-awards-ceremony/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="js_a" class="_5pbx userContent" data-ft="{&quot;tn&quot;:&quot;K&quot;}">
<div id="id_583c10a3228eb0908830821" class="text_exposed_root text_exposed">
<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/14572989_1332299566821015_8299080527848504364_n.jpg"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1646" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/14572989_1332299566821015_8299080527848504364_n.jpg" alt="14572989_1332299566821015_8299080527848504364_n" width="960" height="720" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/14572989_1332299566821015_8299080527848504364_n.jpg 960w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/14572989_1332299566821015_8299080527848504364_n-300x225.jpg 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/14572989_1332299566821015_8299080527848504364_n-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>We&#8217;re on our way to Bristol, feeling very excited! SMASHfestUK has been shortlisted for a national university public engagement award, and we&#8217;re off to the NCCPE Engage Conference where there&#8217;ll be an exhibition of all the finalists, and interviews to decide the ultimate winner. We&#8217;re honoured to be there, in the company of such wonderful other projects, and honoured that the work of all the SMASHfestUK team, the Lewisham community, Middlesex University and the University of <span class="text_exposed_show">Greenwich and the support from all our other partners and sponsors has been recognised. Thank you all!</span></p>
<div class="text_exposed_show">
<p>You can read about the award and all finalists <a href="https://www.publicengagement.ac.uk/work-with-us/engage-competition-2016/competition-finalists">here</a> and <a href="https://www.publicengagement.ac.uk/work-with-us/engage-competition-2016">here</a></p>
<p>Wyn Griffiths, our co-founder, talks about SMASHfestUK and Middlesex University <a href="http://www.mdx.ac.uk/news/2016/11/smashfestuk-shortlisted-for-national-public-engagement-award">here</a></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="_3x-2"></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Engineer Kick Off Meeting is a SMASH!</title>
		<link>./../../../engineer-kick-off-meeting-is-a-smash/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Wow &#8211; what a night! Our inaugural kick off meeting at the Albany theater rocked! The ideas just flowed and our new engineering team just kept going! I&#8217;m not going to let you in on what we have planned but lets just say SMASHfestUk this year is going to be<a class="moretag" href="./../../../engineer-kick-off-meeting-is-a-smash/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender.jpg"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-1641" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-1024x768.jpg" alt="fullsizerender" width="680" height="510" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-1024x768.jpg 1024w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-300x225.jpg 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/11/FullSizeRender-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 680px) 100vw, 680px" /></a></p>
<p>Wow &#8211; what a night!</p>
<p>Our inaugural kick off meeting at the Albany theater rocked! The ideas just flowed and our new engineering team just kept going! I&#8217;m not going to let you in on what we have planned but lets just say SMASHfestUk this year is going to be a blast  &#8211; and I mean that literally! When you have a team like this, the sky&#8217;s the limit! So keep watching this space and we will soon have a programme of events up to entice, engage and enthrall. Make sure that half term week in February is put aside for SMASHfestUK &#8211; its going to go with a bang!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SMASHfestUK is Erupting in Deptford in 2017 – Thank You RAE!</title>
		<link>./../../../smashfestuk-is-erupting-in-deptford-in-2017-thank-you-rae-2/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 12:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1502</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Those ingenious people at the Royal Academy of Engineering have awarded SMASHfestUK an Ingenious grant! The RAE saw how brilliant SMASHfestUK is &#8211; made so by the wonderful people of Deptford. SMASHfestUK is just bowled over and so honoured by the award. Thank you RAE you’re fab!  The Ingenious public<a class="moretag" href="./../../../smashfestuk-is-erupting-in-deptford-in-2017-thank-you-rae-2/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #ffffff;">Those ingenious people at the <a style="color: #ffffff;" href="http://www.raeng.org.uk/"><u><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">Royal Academy of Engineering</span></u></a><span style="color: #000000; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;"><span style="color: #ffffff;"> have awarded SMASHfestUK an</span> <span style="color: #ffffff;">Ingenious grant! The RAE saw how brilliant SMASHfestUK is &#8211; made so by the wonderful people of Deptford. SMASHfestUK is just bowled over and so honoured by the award. Thank you RAE you’re fab!</span></span>  <span style="color: #000000; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;"><span style="color: #ffffff;">The</span> </span><a style="color: #ffffff;" href="http://www.raeng.org.uk/grants-and-prizes/ingenious-grant"><u><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">Ingenious public engagement awards</span></u></a> are for <a style="color: #ffffff;" href="http://www.raeng.org.uk/publications/other/round-ten-ingenious-grant-awardees-2016"><u><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">projects</span></u></a> that engage the public with engineers and engineering. </span></p>
<p><span style="color: #ffffff; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">And engineers are what is required! Because a super volcano is about to erupt in Deptford in February 2017 and life as we know it is under threat…When that happens you know who you need to call! </span></p>
<p><span style="color: #ffffff; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">So get ready to survive the biggest of volcanoes…</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #ffffff; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">If you’re interested in volunteering to help the people of Deptford survive and are an engineer or live locally or go to school/college locally then we want to hear from you! Please contact Tobin May on tobinmay@yahoo.com. </span></p>
<p><span style="color: #ffffff;">Can you survive, do you have what it takes?<span style="color: #000000; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">  </span></span><span style="color: #000000; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;"><span style="color: #ffffff;">Watch this space for the latest updates of all the activities on their way in February half term 2017.</span> </span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SMASHfestUK is Erupting in Deptford in 2017 – Thank You RAE!</title>
		<link>./../../../smashfestuk-is-erupting-in-deptford-in-2017-thank-you-rae/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 16:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Those ingenious people at the Royal Academy of Engineering have awarded SMASHfestUK an Ingenious grant! The RAE saw how brilliant SMASHfestUK is &#8211; made so by the wonderful people of Deptford. SMASHfestUK is just bowled over and so honoured by the award. Thank you RAE you’re fab!  The Ingenious public<a class="moretag" href="./../../../smashfestuk-is-erupting-in-deptford-in-2017-thank-you-rae/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">Those ingenious people at the </span><span style="color: #3366ff;"><a style="color: #3366ff;" href="http://www.raeng.org.uk/"><u><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">Royal Academy of Engineering</span></u></a></span><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;"> have awarded SMASHfestUK an Ingenious grant! The RAE saw how brilliant SMASHfestUK is &#8211; made so by the wonderful people of Deptford. SMASHfestUK is just bowled over and so honoured by the award. Thank you RAE you’re fab!</span><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">  </span><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">The </span><span style="color: #3366ff;"><a style="color: #3366ff;" href="http://www.raeng.org.uk/grants-and-prizes/ingenious-grant"><u><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">Ingenious public engagement awards</span></u></a></span><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;"> are for </span><span style="color: #3366ff;"><a style="color: #3366ff;" href="http://www.raeng.org.uk/publications/other/round-ten-ingenious-grant-awardees-2016"><u><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">projects</span></u></a></span><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;"> that engage the public with engineers and engineering. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">And engineers are what is required! Because a super volcano is about to erupt in Deptford in February 2017 and life as we know it is under threat…When that happens you know who you need to call! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">So get ready to survive the biggest of volcanoes…</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">If you’re interested in volunteering to help the people of Deptford survive and are an engineer or live locally or go to school/college locally then we want to hear from you! Please contact Tobin May on tobinmay@yahoo.com. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">Can you survive, do you have what it takes?</span><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">  </span><span style="font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;">Watch this space for the latest updates of all the activities on their way in February half term 2017. </span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;"> </span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000; font-family: Calibri; font-size: medium;"> </span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
