<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Stephen Lawrence Centre</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>A world where everyone holds the power to employ science and creativity for good.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 10:17:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Lewisham Youth Conference 2015</title>
		<link>./../../../lewishamyouthconference2015/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 10:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events2016]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st February]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[career]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[careers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[choices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deptford Lounge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldsmiths]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middlesex University]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[school]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smashfestUK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South east London]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stephen Lawrence Centre]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Goldsmiths University Saturday 21st February TICKETS: Free but you must register in advance All of the stories and events at SMASHfestUK are inspired by, and designed to uncover how studying subjects in science, technology, engineering and maths can be useful in a myriad of jobs and careers. From architecture, to construction,<a class="moretag" href="./../../../lewishamyouthconference2015/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Goldsmiths University</h2>
<h3>Saturday 21st February</h3>
<h4>TICKETS: <a href="http://www.lyc2015.co.uk/register-your-tickets/" target="_blank">Free but you must register in advance</a></h4>
<p>All of the stories and events at SMASHfestUK are inspired by, and designed to uncover how studying subjects in science, technology, engineering and maths can be useful in a myriad of jobs and careers. From architecture, to construction, from plumbing to sanitation and humanitarian work, from music and film to health and beauty, zoology and lots more, a basic grounding in STEM can open doors to all kind of futures. It also gives you a solid grounding in critical thinking which is useful no matter what you decide to do with your life. The idea that a studying science can only lead to a job in a laboratory wearing a white coat is now history! Come and find out more!</p>
<p><a href="http://www.lyc2015.co.uk/"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-937" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/Screen-Shot-2015-02-05-at-10.01.41-1024x607.png" alt="Screen Shot 2015-02-05 at 10.01.41" width="700" height="415" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/Screen-Shot-2015-02-05-at-10.01.41-1024x607.png 1024w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/Screen-Shot-2015-02-05-at-10.01.41-300x178.png 300w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/Screen-Shot-2015-02-05-at-10.01.41-460x273.png 460w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/Screen-Shot-2015-02-05-at-10.01.41-688x408.png 688w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/Screen-Shot-2015-02-05-at-10.01.41.png 1223w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></a></p>
<div class="infobox_wrapper">LYC 2015 aims to provide young people with an <strong>empowering and inspiring</strong> environment offering a wealth of knowledge in the form of information stands, educational workshops and entertainment! Elevating Success – working in partnership with Lewisham Homes &#8211; the main sponsor, is committed to improving the life chances of young people in its communities. This event will inspire and empower the young people attending, with the ultimate aim of attendees leaving with the knowledge and motivation needed to achieve their dreams. If you would like to book your free ticket to the event, simply fill in the sign up form <a href="http://www.lyc2015.co.uk/register-your-tickets/" target="_blank"><span style="text-decoration: underline;">here</span>.</a> We&#8217;ll see you there!</div>
<div class="infobox_wrapper"></div>
<div class="infobox_wrapper"></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>People&#8217;s Ark (#FRIDGIE)</title>
		<link>./../../../fridgie/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 16:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events2016]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[14 - 22 February]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Albany Theatre]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deptford Lounge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fridgie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[legacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[peoples ark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[posterity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[selfie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South east London]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stephen Lawrence Centre]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world end]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The people&#8217;s ark is a participatory public art installation based around the theme of a time capsule. If an asteroid really was going to flatten everything &#8211; what would you want to leave as a memory of yourself, your life, your legacy for a future generation to find? Our refrigerators<a class="moretag" href="./../../../fridgie/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The people&#8217;s ark is a participatory public art installation based around the theme of a time capsule. If an asteroid really was going to flatten everything &#8211; what would you want to leave as a memory of yourself, your life, your legacy for a future generation to find?</p>
<p>Our refrigerators often tell a fascinating story. Using magnets we pin to them precious photographs, comforting recipes, poems, inspirational thoughts. We spell out words and phrases with magnetic alphabets and words. If you were to leave on thing pinned to your fridge for the future to know who you were&#8230;what would that thing be?</p>
<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/bl-logo-wide.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignleft size-full wp-image-879" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/bl-logo-wide.png" alt="bl-logo-wide" width="453" height="101" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/bl-logo-wide.png 453w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/bl-logo-wide-300x67.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 453px) 100vw, 453px" /></a></p>
<p>SMASHfestUK is working in partnership with the British Library who will be making an archive of all of digital images and content which will be collected from this project and this information will be archived on the SMASHfestUK website as part of the British Library Web Archive Special Collections. One of the things they want to include is this is the UK website (not including huge corporations like Facebook, Twitter, Youtube etc) that are important to you right now at this point in your life. To contribute, pop along to see the installation at the Stephen Lawrence Centre, or visit our Pop-Up Arks at the Deptford Lounge or the Albany theatre during SMASHfestUK week.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>If you can&#8217;t come along but you want to leave a note of your favourite UK website to be archived forever at the British Library, please add in the comments below with your reason for wanting to see this site preserved in its current form as a little piece if history!</p>
<p>[contact-form to=&#8217;info@smashfestuk.com&#8217; subject=&#8217;FRIDGIE PROJECT BRITISH LIBRARY&#8217;]</p>
<p>[contact-field label=&#8217;Name&#8217; type=&#8217;name&#8217; required=&#8217;1&#8217;/]</p>
<p>[contact-field label=&#8217;Email&#8217; type=&#8217;email&#8217; required=&#8217;1&#8217;/]</p>
<p>[contact-field label=&#8217;URL?&#8217; type=&#8217;url&#8217;/]</p>
<p>[contact-field label=&#8217;Why?&#8217; type=&#8217;textarea&#8217; required=&#8217;1&#8217;/][/contact-form]</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MISSION CONTROL (girls only). 18th February. Stephen Lawrence Centre</title>
		<link>./../../../missioncontrol/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 14:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events2016]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[18th February]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stephen Lawrence Centre]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=632</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Would you like to SAVE THE WORLD? Make an asteroid cracking app for your mobile phone? Come to the Stemettes Hack at SMASHfestUK! No previous coding experience necessary, but if you have done some coding before, our experts will teach you how to create complex apps using HTML, CSS and JS.<a class="moretag" href="./../../../missioncontrol/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Would you like to SAVE THE WORLD?</h3>
<h4>Make an asteroid cracking app for your mobile phone?</h4>
<h4>Come to the Stemettes Hack at SMASHfestUK!</h4>
<p>No previous coding experience necessary, but if you have done some coding before, our experts will teach you how to create complex apps using HTML, CSS and JS.</p>
<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/hatslide.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-570" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/hatslide.png" alt="hatslide" width="940" height="300" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/hatslide.png 940w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2015/01/hatslide-300x95.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 940px) 100vw, 940px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>Win prizes!</strong></p>
<p>Food and Laptops provided &#8211; just bring yourself!</p>
<p>TICKETS: Completely FREE! (Thanks to <a href="http://www.refinery.tv/">The Refinery</a> and <a href="http://www.mdx.ac.uk/">Middlesex University</a>)</p>
<p><strong>What is a hackathon?</strong></p>
<p>Hackathons aren&#8217;t about breaking into things! They&#8217;re about bringing people together to create amazing things using computers. We think it&#8217;s really sad that some people have never been to a hackathon or had proper fun with computer science, so we want to give you guys the opportunity to explore and play about in the creative, exciting world of technology.<br />
At this hackathon we&#8217;ll be building to the SMASHfestUK theme: “ASTEROID STRIKE: LEWISHAM&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>Who:</strong></p>
<p>Girls aged 13+</p>
<p>Parents/Guardians. If you&#8217;re under 16, you&#8217;ll need to have an adult with you. On the plus side, we&#8217;d love it if they helped out with making your game or app!</p>
<p>Women (and Men) with a STEM background and are interested in inspiring the next generation. (see below for more details)</p>
<p><strong>When:</strong><br />
MOMENT OF IMPACT DAY!</p>
<p>Wednesday 18th February</p>
<p>10am &#8211; 5:30pm</p>
<p><strong>Where:</strong><br />
The Stephen Lawrence Centre</p>
<p>39 Brookmill Road</p>
<p>London SE8 4HU</p>
<p>Tel: +44 (0) 208 100 2800</p>
<p><strong>What you need to bring:</strong><br />
Yourself and any great ideas you have.<br />
If you have access to a mobile phone, bring it along with you.<br />
We will provide everything else.</p>
<p><strong>Are you interested in helping children learn to code and discover mobile making?</strong></p>
<p>We are looking for adults who have a STEM background to help the girls learn to code, use the AppShed, AppInventor and Thimble webmaker tools and show them the range of possible careers you can do after studying STEM subjects.<br />
All you need to do is provide inspiration and help the girls with their projects when they get stuck.<br />
We will provide food and reasonable transport costs to helpers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
