<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>festival</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>A world where everyone holds the power to employ science and creativity for good.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 11:22:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>SMASHfestUK seeks Producer for RAE Ingenious &#8216;Survival Village and general production duties</title>
		<link>./../../../smashfestuk-seeks-producer-for-rae-ingenious-survival-village-and-general-production-duties/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 15:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[festival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jobs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[outreach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[producer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1487</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SMASHfestUK – RAE ‘Ingenious’ Survival Village and general festival Producer SMASHfestUK is a science and arts mashup festival based in SE London which will return for its third birthday in February 2017. Aimed at young people and their families in SE8, which is a vibrant and culturally diverse community currently<a class="moretag" href="./../../../smashfestuk-seeks-producer-for-rae-ingenious-survival-village-and-general-production-duties/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SMASHfestUK – RAE ‘Ingenious’ Survival Village and general festival Producer</p>
<p>SMASHfestUK is a science and arts mashup festival based in SE London which will return for its third birthday in February 2017. Aimed at young people and their families in SE8, which is a vibrant and culturally diverse community currently underserved by informal science provision, we seek a freelance administrator/assistant producer.</p>
<p>SMASHfestUK has built an audience of 2000 festival attendees and also carries out schools outreach to over 2000 students and is funded by the Wellcome Trust, Arts Council, STFC, Royal Society of Chemistry and Royal Academy of Engineering. At the heart of the festival is the SMASHfestUK Survival Village, which invites the audience to participate in rebuilding after an imagined natural disaster. This year’s storyline is ‘Supervolcano’. Within the ‘Village’ the audience create shelter from available/found materials using basic engineering principles. This year we are developing the concept further to include sanitation, water supply, heating/lighting, and power generation within a coherent interactive experience. Initial work with the core team and early participants has begun.</p>
<p>We need someone to help us with the schedule, production and delivery of the Survival Village. This role will involve liaising with engineers, festival performers, schools, venues and outdoor locations. We need a self-starter who thrives under pressure, is organized, driven, is tenacious and can respond creatively to problems. If this sounds like you (or even if it doesn’t but you like the idea of the job and reckon you could do it well anyway) please tell us why in a short cover letter and send your CV to lindsay@refinery.tv</p>
<p>Job spec:</p>
<p>&#8211; Assistant Producer level</p>
<p>&#8211; PT (flexible) 2days/week (0.4)</p>
<p>&#8211; £200/day</p>
<p>&#8211; Starting September until December, with extension to March for the right candidate</p>
<p>&#8211; Possibility of becoming FT, dependent on funding</p>
<p>Job description:</p>
<p>&#8211; AP required with a passion for widening participation in STEM, the Arts and Design, and creating compelling interactive experiences</p>
<p>&#8211; Must love engineering!</p>
<p>&#8211; Must have great management, organizational and production skills</p>
<p>&#8211; Must have an ‘old school’ passion for production</p>
<p>– (i.e. not scared to pick up a phone!)</p>
<p>&#8211; Ideally will have experience of festival curation and production</p>
<p><a href="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2016/08/SMASHfestUK-RAE-Ingenious-Assistant-Producer-Job-Advert.pdf">SMASHfestUK RAE Ingenious Assistant Producer Job Advert</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
